Tracy Early papers, Inclusive: 1924-2005, Bulk: circa 1940-2005
Baylor University, The Texas Collection
- Magazine and Newspaper Articles, 1947-2005; 1
  - United Methodist Communications: (6 of 6), 1984 (Box 76, Folder 13)
  - United Methodist Reporter: (1 of 4), 1976, 1981 (Box 76, Folder 14)
  - United Methodist Reporter: (2 of 4), 1981 (Box 76, Folder 15)
  - United Methodist Reporter: (3 of 4), 1981 (Box 76, Folder 16)
  - United Methodist Reporter: (4 of 4), 1981-1982 (Box 76, Folder 17)
  - Via Media, 1995-1996 (Box 76, Folder 18)
  - West Texas Angelus, 1986 (Box 77, Folder 1)
  - The Witness: (1 of 2), 1977 (Box 77, Folder 2)
  - The Witness: (2 of 2), 1977-1978 (Box 77, Folder 3)
  - World Report: (1 of 3), 1983-1985 (Box 77, Folder 4)
  - World Report: (2 of 3), 1983 (Box 77, Folder 5)
  - World Report: (3 of 3), 1984 (Box 77, Folder 6)
  - MissioNews: (1 of 5), 1981 (Box 77, Folder 7)
  - MissioNews: (2 of 5), 1982 (Box 77, Folder 8)
  - MissioNews: (3 of 5), 1982 (Box 77, Folder 9)
  - MissioNews: (4 of 5), 1982 (Box 77, Folder 10)
  - MissioNews: (5 of 5), 1982 (Box 77, Folder 11)
  - Worldview: (1 of 4), 1977-1978 (Box 77, Folder 12)
  - Worldview: (2 of 4), 1978 (Box 77, Folder 13)
  - Worldview: (3 of 4), 1978 (Box 77, Folder 14)
  - Worldview: (4 of 4), 1979 (Box 77, Folder 15)
  - General, 1956, 1958 (Box 78, Folder 1)
  - General, 1958-1959 (Box 78, Folder 2)
  - General, 1959 (Box 78, Folder 3)
  - General, 1959 (Box 78, Folder 4)
  - General, 1959 (Box 78, Folder 5)
  - General, 1959-1961 (Box 78, Folder 6)
  - General, 1960, 1962, 1964-1966 (Box 78, Folder 7)
  - General, 1966 (Box 78, Folder 8)
  - General, 1966-1967 (Box 78, Folder 9)
  - General, 1967-1969 (Box 78, Folder 10)
  - General, 1969 (Box 78, Folder 11)
  - General, 1969 (Box 78, Folder 12)
  - General, 1969 (Box 78, Folder 13)
  - General, 1969 (Box 79, Folder 1)
  - General, 1969 (Box 79, Folder 2)
  - General, 1969-1970 (Box 79, Folder 3)
  - General, 1970 (Box 79, Folder 4)
  - General, 1970 (Box 79, Folder 5)
  - General, 1971 (Box 79, Folder 6)
  - General, 1971 (Box 79, Folder 7)
  - General, 1972-1974 (Box 79, Folder 8)
  - General, 1976, 1978-1979, 1981 (Box 79, Folder 9)
  - General, 1984-1986, 1988, 1990 (Box 79, Folder 10)
  - General, 1991 (Box 79, Folder 11)
  - General, 2001 (Box 79, Folder 12)
  - General, undated (Box 79, Folder 13)
- Personal Materials, 1948-2005; 2
  This series contains all Tracy Early’s personal diaries and personal correspondence with family members, most notably his mother, Lillian Early. Also included in this series are awards, certificates, and diplomas that Tracy Early earned over the course of his lifetime. Copies of scrapbooks are included and an index of deaccessioned planners.
  - Diary, 1948-1952 (Box 80, Folder 1)
  - Diary, 1952 (Box 80, Folder 2)
  - Diary, 1953 (Box 80, Folder 3)
  - Diary, 1954 (Box 80, Folder 4)
  - Diary, 1955 (Box 80, Folder 5)
  - Diary, 1956 (Box 80, Folder 6)
  - Diary, 1957 (Box 81, Folder 1)
  - Diary, 1958 (Box 81, Folder 2)
  - Diary, 1959 (Box 81, Folder 3)
  - Diary, 1962 (Box 81, Folder 4)
  - Diary, 1963 (Box 82, Folder 1)
  - Diary, 1964 (Box 82, Folder 2)
  - Diary, 1965 (Box 82, Folder 3)
  - Diary, 1966 (Box 82, Folder 4)
  - Diary, 1967 (Box 83, Folder 1)
  - Diary, 1968 (Box 83, Folder 2)
  - Diary, 1969 (Box 83, Folder 3)
  - Diary, 1970 (Box 83, Folder 4)
  - Diary, 1971 (Box 84, Folder 1)
  - Diary, 1972 (Box 84, Folder 2)
  - Diary, 1973 (Box 84, Folder 3)
  - Diary, 1974 (Box 84, Folder 4)
  - Diary, 1975 (Box 84, Folder 5)
  - Diary, 1976 (Box 84, Folder 6)
  - Diary, 1977 (Box 85, Folder 1)
  - Diary, 1978 (Box 85, Folder 2)
  - Diary, 1979 (Box 85, Folder 3)
  - Diary, 1980 (Box 85, Folder 4)
  - Diary, 1981 (Box 85, Folder 5)
  - Diary, 1982 (Box 85, Folder 6)
  - Diary, 1983 (Box 86, Folder 1)
  - Diary, 1984 (Box 86, Folder 2)
  - Diary, 1985 (Box 86, Folder 3)
  - Diary, 1986 (Box 86, Folder 4)
  - Diary, 1987 (Box 87, Folder 1)
  - Diary, 1988 (Box 87, Folder 2)
  - Diary, 1989 (Box 87, Folder 3)
  - Diary, 1990 (Box 87, Folder 4)
  - Diary, 1991 (Box 88, Folder 1)
  - Diary, 1992 (Box 88, Folder 2)
  - Diary, 1993 (Box 88, Folder 3)
  - Diary, 1994 (Box 88, Folder 4)
  - Diary, 1995 (Box 89, Folder 1)
  - Diary, 1996 (Box 89, Folder 2)
  - Diary, 1997 (Box 89, Folder 3)
  - Diary, 1998 (Box 89, Folder 4)
  - Diary, 1999 (Box 90, Folder 1)
  - Diary, 2000 (Box 90, Folder 2)
  - Diary, 2001 (Box 90, Folder 3)
  - Diary, 2002 (Box 90, Folder 4)
  - Diary, 2003 (Box 91, Folder 1)
  - Diary, 2004 (Box 91, Folder 2)
  - Diary, 2005 (Box 91, Folder 3)
  - Personal Correspondence: From Tracy to Lillian Early: (1 of 4), 1950 (Box 92, Folder 1)
  - Personal Correspondence: From Tracy to Lillian Early: (2 of 4), 1950-1951 (Box 92, Folder 2)
  - Personal Correspondence: From Tracy to Lillian Early: (3 of 4), 1951-1952 (Box 92, Folder 3)
  - Personal Correspondence: From Tracy to Lillian Early: (4 of 4), 1952 (Box 92, Folder 4)
  - Personal Correspondence: From Tracy to Lillian Early: (1 of 4), 1952-1953 (Box 92, Folder 5)
  - Personal Correspondence: From Tracy to Lillian Early: (2 of 4), 1953-1954 (Box 92, Folder 6)
  - Personal Correspondence: From Tracy to Lillian Early: (3 of 4), 1954 (Box 92, Folder 7)
  - Personal Correspondence: From Tracy to Lillian Early: (4 of 4), 1954 (Box 92, Folder 8)
  - Personal Correspondence: From Tracy to Lillian Early: (1 of 3), 1955 (Box 92, Folder 9)
  - Personal Correspondence: From Tracy to Lillian Early: (2 of 3), 1955 (Box 92, Folder 10)
  - Personal Correspondence: From Tracy to Lillian Early: (3 of 3), 1955 (Box 92, Folder 11)
  - Personal Correspondence: From Tracy to Lillian Early: (1 of 3), 1956 (Box 92, Folder 12)
  - Personal Correspondence: From Tracy to Lillian Early: (2 of 3), 1956 (Box 92, Folder 13)
  - Personal Correspondence: From Tracy to Lillian Early: (3 of 3), 1956 (Box 92, Folder 14)
  - Personal Correspondence: From Tracy to Lillian Early: (1 of 4), 1957 (Box 92, Folder 15)
  - Personal Correspondence: From Tracy to Lillian Early: (2 of 4), 1957 (Box 92, Folder 16)
  - Personal Correspondence: From Tracy to Lillian Early: (3 of 4), 1957 (Box 92, Folder 17)
  - Personal Correspondence: From Tracy to Lillian Early: (4 of 4), 1957 (Box 92, Folder 18)
  - Personal Correspondence: From Tracy to Lillian Early: (1 of 3), 1958 (Box 93, Folder 1)
  - Personal Correspondence: From Tracy to Lillian Early: (2 of 3), 1958 (Box 93, Folder 2)
  - Personal Correspondence: From Tracy to Lillian Early: (3 of 3), 1958 (Box 93, Folder 3)
  - Personal Correspondence: From Tracy to Lillian Early: (1 of 4), 1959 (Box 93, Folder 4)
  - Personal Correspondence: From Tracy to Lillian Early: (2 of 4), 1959 (Box 93, Folder 5)
  - Personal Correspondence: From Tracy to Lillian Early: (3 of 4), 1960 (Box 93, Folder 6)
  - Personal Correspondence: From Tracy to Lillian Early: (4 of 4), 1960 (Box 93, Folder 7)
  - Personal Correspondence: From Tracy to Lillian Early: (1 of 4), 1961 (Box 93, Folder 8)
  - Personal Correspondence: From Tracy to Lillian Early: (2 of 4), 1961 (Box 93, Folder 9)
  - Personal Correspondence: From Tracy to Lillian Early: (3 of 4), 1961 (Box 93, Folder 10)
  - Personal Correspondence: From Tracy to Lillian Early: (4 of 4), 1961 (Box 93, Folder 11)
  - Personal Correspondence: From Tracy to Lillian Early: (1 of 3), 1962 (Box 93, Folder 12)
  - Personal Correspondence: From Tracy to Lillian Early: (2 of 3), 1962 (Box 93, Folder 13)
  - Personal Correspondence: From Tracy to Lillian Early: (3 of 3), 1962 (Box 93, Folder 14)
  - Personal Correspondence: From Tracy to Lillian Early: (1 of 4), 1963 (Box 93, Folder 15)
  - Personal Correspondence: From Tracy to Lillian Early: (2 of 4), 1963 (Box 93, Folder 16)
  - Personal Correspondence: From Tracy to Lillian Early: (3 of 4), 1963 (Box 93, Folder 17)
  - Personal Correspondence: From Tracy to Lillian Early: (4 of 4), 1963 (Box 93, Folder 18)
  - Personal Correspondence: From Tracy to Lillian Early: (1 of 4), 1964 (Box 94, Folder 1)
  - Personal Correspondence: From Tracy to Lillian Early: (2 of 4), 1964 (Box 94, Folder 2)
  - Personal Correspondence: From Tracy to Lillian Early: (3 of 4), 1964 (Box 94, Folder 3)
  - Personal Correspondence: From Tracy to Lillian Early: (4 of 4), 1964 (Box 94, Folder 4)
  - Personal Correspondence: From Tracy to Lillian Early: (1 of 3), 1965 (Box 94, Folder 5)
  - Personal Correspondence: From Tracy to Lillian Early: (2 of 3), 1965 (Box 94, Folder 6)
  - Personal Correspondence: From Tracy to Lillian Early: (3 of 3), 1965 (Box 94, Folder 7)
  - Personal Correspondence: From Tracy to Lillian Early: (1 of 4), 1966 (Box 94, Folder 8)
  - Personal Correspondence: From Tracy to Lillian Early: (2 of 4), 1966 (Box 94, Folder 9)
  - Personal Correspondence: From Tracy to Lillian Early: (3 of 4), 1966 (Box 94, Folder 10)
  - Personal Correspondence: From Tracy to Lillian Early: (4 of 4), 1966-1967 (Box 94, Folder 11)
  - Personal Correspondence: From Tracy to Lillian Early, 1968-1970 (Box 94, Folder 12)
  - Personal Correspondence: From Tracy to Lillian Early: (1 of 2), 1971 (Box 94, Folder 13)
  - Personal Correspondence: From Tracy to Lillian Early: (2 of 2), 1971 (Box 94, Folder 14)
  - Personal Correspondence: From Tracy to Lillian Early: (1 of 3), 1972 (Box 94, Folder 15)
  - Personal Correspondence: From Tracy to Lillian Early: (2 of 3), 1972 (Box 94, Folder 16)
  - Personal Correspondence: From Tracy to Lillian Early: (3 of 3), 1972 (Box 94, Folder 17)
  - Personal Correspondence: From Tracy to Lillian Early: (1 of 3), 1973 (Box 94, Folder 18)
  - Personal Correspondence: From Tracy to Lillian Early: (2 of 3), 1973 (Box 94, Folder 19)
  - Personal Correspondence: From Tracy to Lillian Early: (3 of 3), 1973 (Box 94, Folder 20)
  - Personal Correspondence: From Tracy to Lillian Early: (1 of 3), 1974 (Box 94, Folder 21)
  - Personal Correspondence: From Tracy to Lillian Early: (2 of 3), 1974 (Box 94, Folder 22)
  - Personal Correspondence: From Tracy to Lillian Early: (3 of 3), 1974 (Box 94, Folder 23)
  - Personal Correspondence: From Tracy to Lillian Early: (1 of 3), 1975 (Box 95, Folder 1)
  - Personal Correspondence: From Tracy to Lillian Early: (2 of 3), 1975 (Box 95, Folder 2)
  - Personal Correspondence: From Tracy to Lillian Early: (3 of 3), 1975 (Box 95, Folder 3)
  - Personal Correspondence: From Tracy to Lillian Early: (1 of 4), 1976 (Box 95, Folder 4)
  - Personal Correspondence: From Tracy to Lillian Early: (2 of 4), 1976 (Box 95, Folder 5)
  - Personal Correspondence: From Tracy to Lillian Early: (3 of 4), 1976 (Box 95, Folder 6)
  - Personal Correspondence: From Tracy to Lillian Early: (4 of 4), 1976 (Box 95, Folder 7)
  - Personal Correspondence: From Tracy to Lillian Early: (1 of 4), 1977 (Box 95, Folder 8)
  - Personal Correspondence: From Tracy to Lillian Early: (2 of 4), 1977 (Box 95, Folder 9)
  - Personal Correspondence: From Tracy to Lillian Early: (3 of 4), 1977 (Box 95, Folder 10)
  - Personal Correspondence: From Tracy to Lillian Early: (4 of 4), 1977 (Box 95, Folder 11)
  - Personal Correspondence: From Tracy to Lillian Early: (1 of 3), 1978 (Box 95, Folder 12)
  - Personal Correspondence: From Tracy to Lillian Early: (2 of 3), 1978 (Box 95, Folder 13)
  - Personal Correspondence: From Tracy to Lillian Early: (3 of 3), 1978 (Box 95, Folder 14)
  - Personal Correspondence: From Tracy to Lillian Early: (1 of 2), 1979 (Box 95, Folder 15)
  - Personal Correspondence: From Tracy to Lillian Early: (2 of 2), 1979 (Box 95, Folder 16)
  - Personal Correspondence: From Tracy to Lillian Early: (1 of 2), 1980 (Box 96, Folder 1)
  - Personal Correspondence: From Tracy to Lillian Early: (2 of 2), 1980 (Box 96, Folder 2)
  - Personal Correspondence: From Tracy to Lillian Early: (1 of 2), 1981 (Box 96, Folder 3)
  - Personal Correspondence: From Tracy to Lillian Early: (2 of 2), 1982 (Box 96, Folder 4)
  - Personal Correspondence: From Tracy to Lillian Early: (1 of 2), 1982 (Box 96, Folder 5)
  - Personal Correspondence: From Tracy to Lillian Early: (2 of 2), 1982 (Box 96, Folder 6)
  - Personal Correspondence: From Tracy to Lillian Early: (1 of 2), 1983 (Box 96, Folder 7)
  - Personal Correspondence: From Tracy to Lillian Early: (2 of 2), 1983 (Box 96, Folder 8)
  - Personal Correspondence: From Tracy to Lillian Early: (1 of 2), 1984 (Box 96, Folder 9)
  - Personal Correspondence: From Tracy to Lillian Early: (2 of 2), 1984 (Box 96, Folder 10)
  - Personal Correspondence: From Tracy to Lillian Early: (1 of 3), 1985 (Box 96, Folder 11)
  - Personal Correspondence: From Tracy to Lillian Early: (2 of 3), 1985 (Box 96, Folder 12)
  - Personal Correspondence: From Tracy to Lillian Early: (3 of 3), 1985 (Box 96, Folder 13)
  - Personal Correspondence: From Tracy to Lillian Early: (1 of 2), 1986 (Box 96, Folder 14)
  - Personal Correspondence: From Tracy to Lillian Early: (2 of 2), 1986 (Box 96, Folder 15)
  - Personal Correspondence: From Tracy to Lillian Early: (1 of 2), 1987 (Box 96, Folder 16)
  - Personal Correspondence: From Tracy to Lillian Early: (2 of 2), 1987 (Box 96, Folder 17)
  - Personal Correspondence: From Tracy to Lillian Early: (1 of 2), 1988 (Box 97, Folder 1)
  - Personal Correspondence: From Tracy to Lillian Early: (2 of 2), 1988 (Box 97, Folder 2)
  - Personal Correspondence: From Tracy to Lillian Early, 1989 (Box 97, Folder 3)
  - Personal Correspondence: From Tracy to Lillian Early: (1 of 2), 1990 (Box 97, Folder 4)
  - Personal Correspondence: From Tracy to Lillian Early: (2 of 2), 1990 (Box 97, Folder 5)
  - Personal Correspondence: From Tracy to Lillian Early, 1991 (Box 97, Folder 6)
  - Personal Correspondence: From Tracy to Lillian Early: (1 of 2), 1992 (Box 97, Folder 7)
  - Personal Correspondence: From Tracy to Lillian Early: (2 of 2), 1992 (Box 97, Folder 8)
  - Personal Correspondence: From Tracy to Lillian Early: (1 of 4), 1993 (Box 97, Folder 9)
  - Personal Correspondence: From Tracy to Lillian Early: (2 of 4), 1993 (Box 97, Folder 10)
  - Personal Correspondence: From Tracy to Lillian Early: (3 of 4), 1993 (Box 97, Folder 11)
  - Personal Correspondence: From Tracy to Lillian Early: (4 of 4), 1993 (Box 97, Folder 12)
  - Personal Correspondence: From Tracy to Lillian Early: (1 of 2), 1994 (Box 97, Folder 13)
  - Personal Correspondence: From Tracy to Lillian Early: (2 of 2), 1994 (Box 97, Folder 14)
  - Personal Correspondence: From Tracy to Lillian Early: (1 of 2), 1995 (Box 97, Folder 15)
  - Personal Correspondence: From Tracy to Lillian Early: (2 of 2), 1995 (Box 97, Folder 16)
  - Personal Correspondence: From Tracy to Lillian Early: (1 of 2), 1996 (Box 97, Folder 17)
  - Personal Correspondence: From Tracy to Lillian Early: (2 of 2), 1996 (Box 97, Folder 18)
  - Personal Correspondence: From Tracy to Lillian Early, 1997 (Box 98, Folder 1)
  - Personal Correspondence: From Tracy to Lillian Early, 1998 (Box 98, Folder 2)
  - Personal Correspondence: From Tracy to Lillian Early, 1999 (Box 98, Folder 3)
  - Personal Correspondence: From Tracy to Lillian Early, 2000 (Box 98, Folder 4)
  - Personal Correspondence: From Tracy to Lillian Early, 2001 (Box 98, Folder 5)
  - Personal Correspondence: From Tracy to Lillian Early, 2002 (Box 98, Folder 6)
  - Personal Correspondence: From Tracy to Lillian Early, 2003 (Box 98, Folder 7)
  - Personal Correspondence: From Tracy to Lillian Early, 2004 (Box 98, Folder 8)
  - Personal Correspondence: From Tracy to Lillian Early, 2005 (Box 98, Folder 9)
  - Personal Correspondence: Clippings: From Tracy to Lillian Early: (1 of 2), 1972-1979, undated (Box 98, Folder 10)
  - Personal Correspondence: From Tracy to Lillian Early: (2 of 2), 1983-1995, undated (Box 98, Folder 11)
  - Personal Correspondence: From Lillian to Tracy Early, 1941, 1951 (Box 98, Folder 12)
  - Personal Correspondence: From Lillian to Tracy Early, 1951 (Box 98, Folder 13)
  - Personal Correspondence: From Lillian to Tracy Early, 1952 (Box 98, Folder 14)
  - Personal Correspondence: From Lillian to Tracy Early, 1952 (Box 98, Folder 15)
  - Personal Correspondence: From Lillian to Tracy Early, 1953 (Box 98, Folder 16)
  - Personal Correspondence: From Lillian to Tracy Early, 1953 (Box 98, Folder 17)
  - Personal Correspondence: From Lillian to Tracy Early, 1954 (Box 98, Folder 18)
  - Personal Correspondence: From Lillian to Tracy Early, 1954 (Box 98, Folder 19)
  - Personal Correspondence: From Lillian to Tracy Early, 1954 (Box 98, Folder 20)
  - Personal Correspondence: From Lillian to Tracy Early, 1955 (Box 99, Folder 1)
  - Personal Correspondence: From Lillian to Tracy Early, 1955 (Box 99, Folder 2)
  - Personal Correspondence: From Lillian to Tracy Early, 1955 (Box 99, Folder 3)
  - Personal Correspondence: From Lillian to Tracy Early, 1955 (Box 99, Folder 4)
  - Personal Correspondence: From Lillian to Tracy Early, 1955 (Box 99, Folder 5)
  - Personal Correspondence: From Lillian to Tracy Early, 1955 (Box 99, Folder 6)
  - Personal Correspondence: From Lillian to Tracy Early, 1955 (Box 99, Folder 7)
  - Personal Correspondence: From Lillian to Tracy Early, 1956 (Box 99, Folder 8)
  - Personal Correspondence: From Lillian to Tracy Early, 1956 (Box 99, Folder 9)
  - Personal Correspondence: From Lillian to Tracy Early, 1956 (Box 99, Folder 10)
  - Personal Correspondence: From Lillian to Tracy Early, 1956 (Box 99, Folder 11)
  - Personal Correspondence: From Lillian to Tracy Early, 1956 (Box 99, Folder 12)
  - Personal Correspondence: From Lillian to Tracy Early, 1957 (Box 99, Folder 13)
  - Personal Correspondence: From Lillian to Tracy Early, 1957 (Box 99, Folder 14)
  - Personal Correspondence: From Lillian to Tracy Early, 1957 (Box 99, Folder 15)
  - Personal Correspondence: From Lillian to Tracy Early, 1957 (Box 99, Folder 16)
  - Personal Correspondence: From Lillian to Tracy Early, 1957 (Box 99, Folder 17)
  - Personal Correspondence: From Lillian to Tracy Early, 1957 (Box 99, Folder 18)
  - Personal Correspondence: From Lillian to Tracy Early, 1957 (Box 99, Folder 19)
  - Personal Correspondence: From Lillian to Tracy Early, 1958 (Box 100, Folder 1)
  - Personal Correspondence: From Lillian to Tracy Early, 1958 (Box 100, Folder 2)
  - Personal Correspondence: From Lillian to Tracy Early, 1958 (Box 100, Folder 3)
  - Personal Correspondence: From Lillian to Tracy Early, 1958 (Box 100, Folder 4)
  - Personal Correspondence: From Lillian to Tracy Early, 1958 (Box 100, Folder 5)
  - Personal Correspondence: From Lillian to Tracy Early, 1958 (Box 100, Folder 6)
  - Personal Correspondence: From Lillian to Tracy Early, 1959 (Box 100, Folder 7)
  - Personal Correspondence: From Lillian to Tracy Early, 1959 (Box 100, Folder 8)
  - Personal Correspondence: From Lillian to Tracy Early, 1959 (Box 100, Folder 9)
  - Personal Correspondence: From Lillian to Tracy Early, 1959 (Box 100, Folder 10)
  - Personal Correspondence: From Lillian to Tracy Early, 1959 (Box 100, Folder 11)
  - Personal Correspondence: From Lillian to Tracy Early, 1960 (Box 100, Folder 12)
  - Personal Correspondence: From Lillian to Tracy Early, 1960 (Box 100, Folder 13)
  - Personal Correspondence: From Lillian to Tracy Early, 1960 (Box 100, Folder 14)
  - Personal Correspondence: From Lillian to Tracy Early, 1960 (Box 100, Folder 15)
  - Personal Correspondence: From Lillian to Tracy Early, 1960 (Box 100, Folder 16)
  - Personal Correspondence: From Lillian to Tracy Early, 1961 (Box 101, Folder 1)
  - Personal Correspondence: From Lillian to Tracy Early, 1961 (Box 101, Folder 2)
  - Personal Correspondence: From Lillian to Tracy Early, 1961 (Box 101, Folder 3)
  - Personal Correspondence: From Lillian to Tracy Early, 1962 (Box 101, Folder 4)
  - Personal Correspondence: From Lillian to Tracy Early, 1962 (Box 101, Folder 5)
  - Personal Correspondence: From Lillian to Tracy Early, 1962-1963 (Box 101, Folder 6)
  - Personal Correspondence: From Lillian to Tracy Early, 1963 (Box 101, Folder 7)
  - Personal Correspondence: From Lillian to Tracy Early, 1963 (Box 101, Folder 8)
  - Personal Correspondence: From Lillian to Tracy Early, 1964 (Box 101, Folder 9)
  - Personal Correspondence: From Lillian to Tracy Early, 1964 (Box 101, Folder 10)
  - Personal Correspondence: From Lillian to Tracy Early, 1964 (Box 101, Folder 11)
  - Personal Correspondence: From Lillian to Tracy Early, 1965 (Box 101, Folder 12)
  - Personal Correspondence: From Lillian to Tracy Early, 1965 (Box 101, Folder 13)
  - Personal Correspondence: From Lillian to Tracy Early, 1965-1966 (Box 101, Folder 14)
  - Personal Correspondence: From Lillian to Tracy Early, 1967 (Box 101, Folder 15)
  - Personal Correspondence: From Lillian to Tracy Early, 1967 (Box 101, Folder 16)
  - Personal Correspondence: From Lillian to Tracy Early, 1967 (Box 101, Folder 17)
  - Personal Correspondence: From Lillian to Tracy Early, 1967 (Box 101, Folder 18)
  - Personal Correspondence: From Lillian to Tracy Early, 1968 (Box 101, Folder 19)
  - Personal Correspondence: From Lillian to Tracy Early, 1968-1969 (Box 101, Folder 20)
  - Personal Correspondence: From Lillian to Tracy Early, 1969 (Box 101, Folder 21)
  - Personal Correspondence: From Lillian to Tracy Early, 1969-1970 (Box 101, Folder 22)
  - Personal Correspondence: From Lillian to Tracy Early, 1970 (Box 102, Folder 1)
  - Personal Correspondence: From Lillian to Tracy Early, 1970-1971 (Box 102, Folder 2)
  - Personal Correspondence: From Lillian to Tracy Early, 1971 (Box 102, Folder 3)
  - Personal Correspondence: From Lillian to Tracy Early, 1971-1972 (Box 102, Folder 4)
  - Personal Correspondence: From Lillian to Tracy Early, 1972-1973 (Box 102, Folder 5)
  - Personal Correspondence: From Lillian to Tracy Early, 1973 (Box 102, Folder 6)
  - Personal Correspondence: From Lillian to Tracy Early, 1974 (Box 102, Folder 7)
  - Personal Correspondence: From Lillian to Tracy Early, 1974-1975 (Box 102, Folder 8)
  - Personal Correspondence: From Lillian to Tracy Early, 1975 (Box 102, Folder 9)
  - Personal Correspondence: From Lillian to Tracy Early, 1976 (Box 102, Folder 10)
  - Personal Correspondence: From Lillian to Tracy Early, 1976-1977 (Box 102, Folder 11)
  - Personal Correspondence: From Lillian to Tracy Early, 1977-1978 (Box 102, Folder 12)
  - Personal Correspondence: From Lillian to Tracy Early, 1977-1978 (Box 102, Folder 13)
  - Personal Correspondence: From Lillian to Tracy Early, 1978-1979 (Box 102, Folder 14)
  - Personal Correspondence: From Lillian to Tracy Early, 1979 (Box 102, Folder 15)
  - Personal Correspondence: From Lillian to Tracy Early, 1980 (Box 102, Folder 16)
  - Personal Correspondence: From Lillian to Tracy Early, 1980-1981 (Box 102, Folder 17)
  - Personal Correspondence: From Lillian to Tracy Early, 1981-1982 (Box 102, Folder 18)
  - Personal Correspondence: From Lillian to Tracy Early, 1982 (Box 102, Folder 19)
  - Personal Correspondence: From Lillian to Tracy Early, 1982-1983 (Box 102, Folder 20)
  - Personal Correspondence: From Lillian to Tracy Early, 1983-1984 (Box 102, Folder 21)
  - Personal Correspondence: From Lillian to Tracy Early, 1984 (Box 103, Folder 1)
  - Personal Correspondence: From Lillian to Tracy Early, 1984-1985 (Box 103, Folder 2)
  - Personal Correspondence: From Lillian to Tracy Early, 1985-1986 (Box 103, Folder 3)
  - Personal Correspondence: From Lillian to Tracy Early, 1986-1987 (Box 103, Folder 4)
  - Personal Correspondence: From Lillian to Tracy Early, 1987 (Box 103, Folder 5)
  - Personal Correspondence: From Lillian to Tracy Early, 1987-1988 (Box 103, Folder 6)
  - Personal Correspondence: From Lillian to Tracy Early, 1988-1989 (Box 103, Folder 7)
  - Personal Correspondence: From Lillian to Tracy Early, 1989 (Box 103, Folder 8)
  - Personal Correspondence: From Lillian to Tracy Early, 1990 (Box 103, Folder 9)
  - Personal Correspondence: From Lillian to Tracy Early, 1990-1991 (Box 103, Folder 10)